Edrian V. Delos Reyes

Web Developer • Web Accessibility Expert

Professional Summary

A dedicated developer focused on back-end combined with the expertise in digital accessibility following Web Content Accessibility Guidelines. As a working student, I achieved consistent academic excellence as I led a team of Computer Trainers and provided technical support to various professionals while pursuing the field of web development during my internship.

Contact

Quezon City, Philippines

⊠ edrianvdr@gmail.com

+639292259697

in in/edriandelosreyes

EdrianDelosReyes.netlify.app

• github.com/edrianvdr

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Divine Mercy College Foundation, Inc. 2019, 2021 – 2024

Achievements:

- Academic Excellence Awardee (1st year to 4th year)
- Creator of our college department's logo

Work Experience

Web Developer Intern

Virtualahan, Mar 2024 - May 2024

Developed on back-end in a learning management system.

- Designed and updated the MySQL database of the system.
- Implemented accessibility features following WCAG.
- Incorporated Tailwind CSS on the Laravel project.
- Implemented security with hashing, auth & Eloquent ORM.

Live Streaming Technician

Elmer Francisco Industries, Aug 2020 – Dec 2021

- Supported all the live show hosts on the technical side.
- Set and facilitated meetings with the hosts.
- Maintained high quality audio and visual presentation.
- Enhanced posts of every streams on Facebook Page.
- Reported analytics and insights to different hosts.

Computer Trainer

ATRIEV I.T. Center Aug 2018 – Aug 2020 (Project-based)

- Trained over 50 students in WordPress, MS Office, social media marketing, and digital content creation.
- Led a team of Computer Trainers.
- Created and enhanced e-learning materials.

Skills

- Developed my e-commerce website thesis system as a full-stack developer using Laravel, MySQL, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, and Livewire while adhering to W3C Accessibility standards.
- Created a website portfolio using ReactJS and Tailwind, then deployed it on Netlify and GitHub.
- Adapted quickly from Code Igniter and Bootstrap to Laravel and Tailwind during internship.
- Followed deadlines and tasks utilizing Jira and Notion as project management tools.
- Explored the basics of WordPress, Node.Js, Java, and Python.
- Demonstrated strong communication skills in writing and speaking while collaborating with a team.